<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ArnoldSM - Portfolio &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ArnoldSM - Portfolio &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Second Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the second post of the website and the first post that is hosted on the website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Arnold—a hybrid of spreadsheets and code, auditing financial systems by day and engineering AI tools by night. My career is a Venn diagram: one circle in corporate rigor (BDDK/KGK compliance, HR analytics), the other in chaos (Cappadocia cave hotels, concert production). The overlap? Relentless problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trained in environmental engineering, I dissect data with lab precision. Built software to automate bureaucracy, track employee milestones, and streamline audits—because even compliance can have a brain. Fluent in Turkish, English, and Python.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can contact me via Email, Discord, Twitter, or LinkedIn. I usually respond within a day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With 22+ years of hands-on experience in tech, my journey started from sheer curiosity—tinkering with design tools, internet utilities, and whatever software I could get my hands on. That curiosity evolved into a practical mindset: learn fast, adapt quicker, and figure things out as I go. Technology isn’t just a skillset for me—it’s a second language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My professional path has been as versatile as my interests, spanning financial auditing, HR, data control, and live event production. Each role added new layers to how I approach systems, people, and problem-solving. I’ve worked on the ground and behind the scenes, always looking for smarter, more efficient ways to do things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are some of my recent projects that showcase my skills and interests in technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
